Guide to the David Locke Webster Papers SC0131
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, 1918-1966; Series D
  - Williams, John A. Model Studies of Long Wave Amplification by Circular Islands and Submarine Seamounts (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Tsunamis papers received from BP, August 1966 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Electrical Principles: typescript, Chs. 1-7, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Electrical Principles: typescript, Chs. 8-12, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Electrical Theory: notes and articles (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Directions for speed test (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Misc. aeronautical reports (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - French report on the DH-4 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - HNR, On the Navigation of Airplanes, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Photography of bomb trajectories, Duff & Sieg (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Tests of some instruments at Langley Field (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Course on airplane instruments, Sep-18 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2017-233
  - "Reminiscences of a Rolling Stone," by DLW, 1975-1976 (Box 1)